

# HAMZA KHAN

# Software Engineer

I am a passionate full stack developer with 4 years experience working for many companies and startups, I love to create applications around web with neat and clean code using best practices. Launched multiple projects with different teams. I always ready for new challanges.

## **Contact Info**

+92341-2682080

🔼 hamzakhann66@gmail.com

www.hamzakhann.com

www.github.com/Hamzakhann

in www.linkedin.com/in/hamzakhann66

#### **Education**

ILMA University - Formerly IBT (2017 - 2021) BSCS, Computer Science

**Govt. Degree College** (2015 - 2016) Intermediate Pre Engineering

Aligarh institute of technology (2011 - 2014)

DAE Electrical Engineering

## **Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Sass
- React.js
- Vue.js
- Gatsby.js
- Next.js
- GIT
- Firebase

- Javascript
- Typescript
- Node.js
- Express.js
- Graphal
- Mongodb
- Mysql
- AWS
- Web 3.0

## **Work Experience**

FULL STACK ENGINEER (2021 - 2022)

ARCHITECTED RELATIONS

Working as a software development associate and developing amazing products for clients throughout the world.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER (2020 - 2021)

<u>MINTDROPZ</u>

Build full stack Web 3.0 applications for web. Deliver clean, readable and efficient solutions following the best practices and standards.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (2019 - 2020)
RIGHTBOUND

Responsible for developing, designing, modeling and documenting the software solutions. Worked on complex charts, tables and complex data structure.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (2018 - 2019)
HOLON-IQ

Working on tables charts data modelling and APIs integration creating pages with latest frontend technology.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (2018 - 2019)

**RUVIVO** 

Write and test code, refining and rewriting it as necessary, and communicate with any programmers involved in the project. Design AI based application using AWS services.

(2017 - 2018)

PANACLOUD PVT LTD

Selected as a bootcamper & learnt latest technologies

